We'll arrange for her to move in across the
hall so he can pathetically moon over her.
- Okay, that was uncalled for.
- You started it, dude.
[GLASS CLINKING]
(Gablehouser:)Could I have everyone's attention,
please?
(Gablehouser:)What a wonderful occasion this is.
(Gablehouser:)And how fortunate that it should
fall on Take Your Daughter to Work Day.
(Gablehouser:)We're here to welcome Mr. Dennis Kim
to our little family.
(Sheldon(sarcastically):)Welcome, Dennis Kim.
(Gablehouser:)Mr. Kim was not only the valedictorian
at Stanford University...
(Gablehouser:)...he is also the youngest recipient
of the prestigious Stevenson Award.
(Sheldon:)Youngest till the cyborgs rise up.
(Gablehouser:)And now, without any further ado...
(Gablehouser:)...let me introduce the man of the hour,
Mr. Dennis Kim.
Dennis? Dennis.
(Leonard:)What?
(Gablehouser:)Would you like to tell us
about your upcoming research?